{
  "0": {
    "question": "Who made the game BombSquad?",
    "options": ["Mrmaxmeier", "The Mikirog", "Eric Froemling", "Froshlee"],
    "answers": ["3", "Eric Froemling"]
  },
  "1": {
    "question": "What is the name of health powerup in original BombSquad game in `How to play` window by default?",
    "options": ["health", "survive", "Med-Pack", "Curse-Cancel"],
    "answers": ["3", "Med-Pack"]
  },
  "2": {
    "question": "What is the name of health powerup in original BombSquad game in `bsPowerup.py` script by default?",
    "options": ["health", "survive", "Med-Pack", "Curse-Cancel"],
    "answers": ["1", "health"]
  },
  "3": {
    "question": "What is the name of the powerup in BombSquad game which gives you a BuddyBunny?",
    "options": ["BuddyBunny", "bunny", "buddy-bunny", "buddy"],
    "answers": ["2", "bunny"]
  },
  "4": {
    "question": "Which mod script adds `Super Smash` game in BombSquad?",
    "options": ["superSmash.py", "SnoBallz.py", "smash.py", "snake.py"],
    "answers": ["3", "smash.py"]
  },
  "5": {
    "question": "Which powerup lets you whip out three bombs in a row in original BombSquad by default?",
    "options": ["Triple-Bombs", "Energy-Shield", "Trigger-Bombs", "tripleBombs"],
    "answers": ["1", "Triple-Bombs", "4", "tripleBombs"]
  },
  "6": {
    "question": "Which of the following is not one of the control buttons in original BombSquad game by default?",
    "options": ["Punch", "Bomb", "Jump", "Fly"],
    "answers": ["4", "Fly"]
  },
  "7": {
    "question": "A BombSquad game's dedicated server can be configured to allow how many players?",
    "options": ["6", "9", "50", "99"],
    "answers": ["4", "99"]
  },
  "8": {
    "question": "Which of the following windows is used for playing online?",
    "options": ["Gather", "Play", "Online", "Watch"],
    "answers": ["1", "Gather"]
  },
  "9": {
    "question": "Which of the following is not a window of the original BombSquad game by default?",
    "options": ["Gather", "Play", "Online", "Watch"],
    "answers": ["3", "Online"]
  },
  "10": {
    "question": "Which map is shown on the main menu in original BombSquad game by default?",
    "options": ["The Pad", "Football Stadium", "Hockey Stadium", "Rampage"],
    "answers": ["1", "The Pad"]
  }
}